Guide to the Duke Photography Faculty and Staff Photographs, circa 1960s-2003 UA.12.03.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Faculty and Staff Photographs, 1
  - Verhey, Allen, 1642
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Vesilind, Aarne, 1643
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Vettas, Nikolaos, 1644
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Vick, Paul, 1645
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Vidmar, Neil, 1646
    - Photographs (Box 23)
    - Negatives (Box 41)
  - Vieweg, Johannes, 1647
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Vigdor, Jacob and Elizabeth, 1648
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Villanueva, Elia, 1649
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Vilter, Jeff, 1650
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Vincent, James L., 1651
    - Photographs (Box 23)
    - Negatives (Box 41)
  - Vinesett, Ava, 1652
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Vinoly, Rafael, 1653
    - Negatives (Box 42)
  - Virgin, Lawrence, 1654
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Virtul, Janice, 1655
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Viscusi, Kip, 1656
    - Photographs (Box 23)
    - Negatives (Box 42)
  - Vo-Dihn, Tuan, 1657
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Vogel, Steven, 1658
    - Photographs (Box 23)
    - Negatives (Box 42)
  - Voisin, Carol, 1659
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Von der Heyden, Karl, 1660
    - Photographs (Box 23)
    - Negatives (Box 42)
  - Von Ramm, Olaf, 1661
    - Photographs (Box 23)
    - Negatives (Box 42)
  - Voss, Zannie Giraud, 1662
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Wacker, Grant, 1663
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Wagoner, Richard, 1664
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Wainwright, Geoffrey, 1665
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Wainwright, S. A., 1666
    - Photographs (Box 23)
    - Negatives (Box 42)
  - Wake, Eula A., 1667
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Wald, Priscilla, 1668
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Walker, Connie, 1669
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Walker, Lana, 1670
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Wall, Wendy, 1671
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Wallace, Maurice, 1672
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Wallenstein, Steve, 1673
    - Photographs (Box 23)
    - Negatives (Box 42)
  - Walmer, David, 1674
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Wang, Jim, 1675
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Ward, Ben, 1676
    - Photographs (Box 23)
    - Negatives (Box 42)
  - Warren, Warren, 1677
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Wasiolek, Sue, 1678
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Waters, Bucky, 1679
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Watkins, Lana, 1680
    - Negatives (Box 42)
  - Watson, Joyce, 1681
    - Negatives (Box 42)
  - Webb-Mitchell, Brett, 1682
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Weber, Thomas, 1683
    - Negatives (Box 42)
  - Webster, George, 1684
    - Negatives (Box 42)
  - Weidner, Alison, 1685
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Weinhold, Kent, 1686
    - Negatives (Box 42)
  - Weintraub, Roy, 1687
    - Photographs (Box 23)
    - Negatives (Box 42)
  - Weistart, John, 1688
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Welch, C. Eileen Watts, 1689
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Wellman, Dave, 1690
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Wells, Richard L., 1691
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Wells, Sam, 1692
    - Negatives (Box 42)
  - Wells, Sam (Chapel), 1693
    - Negatives (Box 42)
  - Welna, Chris, 1694
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Welsh-Bohmer, Kathleen, 1695
    - Negatives (Box 42)
  - Wenthe, Michael, 1696
    - Photographs (Box 23)
  - Werber, Bill, 1697
    - Photographs (Box 24)
  - Wertenbroch, Klaus, 1698
    - Photographs (Box 24)
  - Westbrook, Sherri, 1699
    - Photographs (Box 24)
  - Wester, Thad B., 1700
    - Photographs (Box 24)
  - Westerfield Tucker, Karen, 1701
    - Photographs (Box 24)
  - Wettach, Jane, 1702
    - Photographs (Box 24)
    - Negatives (Box 42)
  - Wharton, Annabel, 1703
    - Negatives (Box 42)
  - Whetten-Goldstein, Kathryn, 1704
    - Negatives (Box 42)
      Includes images with Sherman James
  - White, Fred, 1705
    - Photographs (Box 24)
  - White, Judith, 1706
    - Photographs (Box 24)
  - White, Richard, 1707
    - Photographs (Box 24)
    - Negatives (Box 42)
  - Whitehead Family, 1708
    - Negatives (Box 42)
  - Whiteside, Tom, 1709
    - Photographs (Box 24)
  - Wiegman, Robin, 1710
    - Photographs (Box 24)
  - Wiener, Jonathan, 1711
    - Photographs (Box 24)
    - Negatives (Box 42)
  - Wigen, Karen, 1712
    - Photographs (Box 24)
  - Wilder, Pelham, 1713
    - Photographs (Box 24)
  - Wilder, Sterly, 1714
    - Photographs (Box 24)
  - Wilkerson, Jim, 1715
    - Photographs (Box 24)
  - Wilkinson, Dottie, 1716
    - Photographs (Box 24)
  - Wilkinson, Scott, 1717
    - Photographs (Box 24)
  - Willett, Rebecca, 1718
    - Photographs (Box 24)
  - Williams, Christina, 1719
    - Photographs (Box 24)
  - Williams, Kraig, 1720
    - Negatives (Box 42)
  - Williams, Larry, 1721
    - Negatives (Box 42)
  - Williams, Morris, 1722
    - Photographs (Box 24)
    - Negatives (Box 42)
  - Williams, Neil, 1723
    - Photographs (Box 24)
  - Williams, Peter, 1724
    - Negatives (Box 42)
  - Williams, Redford, 1725
    - Photographs (Box 24)
    - Negatives (Box 42)
  - Williams, Robert, 1726
    - Photographs (Box 24)
  - Williams, S. Mark, 1727
    - Negatives (Box 42)
  - Williams, Sandy, 1728
    - Photographs (Box 24)
    - Negatives (Box 42)
  - Williams, Sheila, 1729
    - Photographs (Box 24)
  - Williams, Tammy, 1730
    - Photographs (Box 24)
  - Williard, Hunt, 1731
    - Photographs (Box 24)
    - Negatives (Box 42)
  - Willimon, William H., 1732
    - Photographs (Box 24)
  - Willimon, William, H., 1733
    - Negatives (Box 42)
  - Willis, John, 1734
    - Photographs (Box 24)
    - Negatives (Box 42)
  - Wilson, Bill, 1735
    - Photographs (Box 24)
  - Wilson, Erin, 1736
    - Photographs (Box 24)
    - Negatives (Box 42)
  - Wilson, Gerald, 1737
    - Photographs (Box 24)
    - Negatives (Box 42)
  - Wilson, Heather, 1738
    - Photographs (Box 24)
  - Wilson, Joanne, 1739
    - Negatives (Box 42)
  - Wilson, Peter, 1740
    - Photographs (Box 24)
  - Winn, Michelle, 1741
    - Photographs (Box 24)
  - Wioskowski, Rhonda, 1742
    - Photographs (Box 24)
  - Wissoker, Ken, 1743
    - Photographs (Box 24)
    - Negatives (Box 43)
  - Witzleben, Karen, 1744
    - Photographs (Box 24)
  - Wolever, Mark, 1745
    - Photographs (Box 24)
  - Wolfe, Tom, 1746
    - Photographs (Box 24)
    - Negatives (Box 43)
  - Wong, Fulton, 1747
    - Negatives (Box 43)
  - Wood, Peter, 1748
    - Photographs (Box 24)
    - Negatives (Box 43)
  - Woodard, Mike, 1749
    - Negatives (Box 43)
  - Woodbury, Max, 1750
    - Negatives (Box 43)
  - Woodruff, Judy, 1751
    - Photographs (Box 24)
  - Woods-Powell, C. T., 1752
    - Photographs (Box 24)
  - Woolley, Barbara, 1753
    - Photographs (Box 24)
  - Worth, Lucy, 1754
    - Photographs (Box 24)
  - Wray, Greg, 1755
    - Photographs (Box 24)
  - Wright, Carol, 1756
    - Photographs (Box 24)
  - Wright, George, 1757
    - Photographs (Box 24)
    - Negatives (Box 43)
  - Wrigley, Bill, 1758
    - Negatives (Box 43)
  - Wulforst, Jim, 1759
    - Photographs (Box 24)
    - Negatives (Box 43)
  - Wyngaarden, Jim, 1760
    - Negatives (Box 43)
  - Wynkoop, Rodney, 1761
    - Photographs (Box 24)
    - Negatives (Box 43)
  - Yaggy, Duncan, 1762
    - Photographs (Box 24)
  - Yang, Dennis, 1763
    - Photographs (Box 24)
  - Yang, Jun, 1764
    - Photographs (Box 24)
  - Yang, Weitao, 1765
    - Photographs (Box 24)
  - Yang, Zhong Ping, 1766
    - Photographs (Box 24)
  - Yarborough, John, 1767
    - Photographs (Box 24)
  - Ybarra, Gary, 1768
    - Photographs (Box 24)
      Includes images with Martha Absher
  - Yoh, Spike, 1769
    - Photographs (Box 25)
    - Negatives (Box 43)
  - Yohe, William, 1770
    - Photographs (Box 25)
  - You, Lingchong, 1771
    - Photographs (Box 25)
  - Young, Evan, 1772
    - Photographs (Box 25)
  - Young, Gwynne, 1773
    - Photographs (Box 25)
  - Young, Myron, 1774
    - Photographs (Box 25)
  - Younger, John, 1775
    - Photographs (Box 25)
  - Yuan, Fan, 1776
    - Photographs (Box 25)
  - Zapf, Donna, 1777
    - Negatives (Box 43)
  - Zauscher, Stefan, 1778
    - Photographs (Box 25)
  - Zechini, Jimmy, 1779
    - Photographs (Box 25)
  - Zhong, Pei, 1780
    - Photographs (Box 25)
    - Negatives (Box 43)
  - Zhou, Lin, 1781
    - Photographs (Box 25)
  - Zidar, James, 1782
    - Photographs (Box 25)
  - Zimmerman, Pam, 1783
    - Photographs (Box 25)
  - Zipkin, Paul, 1784
    - Photographs (Box 25)
  - Zsuppan, Feri, 1785
    - Photographs (Box 25)